Guide to the Acton Visual Materials at La Pietra MSS.LaPietra.001
Villa La Pietra
- Series I: The Actons
  - Subseries C: Acton, Harold (HA)
    - 12 HA with others (not at Villa La Pietra)
      - HA with a lady, undated; cuid1289 (Photo-album 9, Image 4)
      - HA with a lady [Anne Rosse], undated; cuid1290 (Photo-album 9, Image 5)
      - HA [with Michael and Anne Rosse], undated; cuid1291 (Photo-album 9, Image 6)
      - HA [with Michael and Anne Rosse and their sons], undated; cuid1292 (Photo-album 9, Image 7-8.)
      - HA with others, 1952; cuid1293 (Photo-album 9, Image 8a.)
        Annotated on the verso "Mont Blanc" and dated 1952.
      - HA with Bernard Berenson at Villa I Tatti, ca. 1950s; cuid1294 (Photo-album 9, Image 9)
      - HA with Bernard Berenson and Nicky Mariano (left) in the harbour of Procida (Napoli) on board the ferry to Ischia, June, 1952; cuid1295 (Photo-album 9, Image 10)
      - HA with Nicky Mariano in Ischia, 1952; cuid1296 (Photo-album 9, Image 11)
      - HA with a boy, 1957; cuid1297 (Photo-album 9, Image 12)
      - HA with a young man, ca. 1957; cuid1298 (Photo-album 9, Image 12a.)
        On the recto of a postcard addressed on the verso to "Baron Harold Acton" dated 31.12.57 with one signature illegible and the other "affettuosi saluti, Francesco".
      - HA with a couple at a restaurant, undated; cuid1299 (Photo-album 9, Image 13)
      - HA with a couple at Pisa, by the Leaning Tower, undated; cuid1300 (Photo-album 9, Image 14)
      - HA with others outside St Clothilde [Paris], France, 1952; cuid1301 (Photo-album 9, Image 15-16.)
        Annotated on the verso, Color prints, 1952.
      - HA with a man in a garden, undated; cuid1302 (Photo-album 9, Image 17)
      - HA at a party [in Milano], undated; cuid1303 (Photo-album 9, Image 18-20.)
        Photos by Fotoverri, Milano.
      - HA with others at a party, 1954; cuid1304 (Photo-album 9, Image 21-23.)
      - HA with others, including his mother HMA, undated; cuid1305 (Photo-album 9, Image 24)
      - HA in Tripoli, visiting Anna Maria Cicogna and Marina Luling, daughters of Count Volpi, former Governor of Tripoli who lived there at the Villa Volpi, Sciara sidi i Khalifa, 1957; cuid1306 (Photo-album 9, Image 25-32.)
      - HA with a lady at a restaurant in a port (or on board ship), undated; cuid1307 (Photo-album 9, Image 32a.)
      - HA with two men at a restaurant, undated; cuid1308 (Photo-album 9, Image 33-34.)
      - HA with a lady, undated; cuid1309 (Photo-album 9, Image 35)
        Photo by Publifoto, Torino.
      - HA with Alexander Zielcke, undated; cuid1310 (Photo-album 9, Image 36)
      - HA with Jean Cootes, the wife of the US Consul in Firenze, Merritt Cootes, at a party, undated; cuid1311 (Photo-album 9, Image 37-38.)
        Photo by Fotoreporter Pollazzi, Firenze.
      - HA with Andreola Corsini at a party, undated; cuid1312 (Photo-album 9, Image 39-40.)
      - HA at a dinner party at the Villa Maser, near Treviso on 19 February, undated; cuid1313 (Photo-album 9, Image 40a.-40b.)
        Annotated on the recto. Photos by Comaron, Onigo (Treviso).
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret and Lord Snowdon and others, ca. 1965-1968; cuid1314 (Photo-album 9, Image 41-45.)
        In the gardens by the swimming pool of Villa Capponi, Florence.
      - HA with Lord Snowdon, Piazzale Michelangelo, Firenze, 1968; cuid1315 (Photo-album 9, Image 46)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret, at a cafè on the motorway (on their way to Marlia), August, 1974; cuid1316 (Photo-album 9, Image 47)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret, and a man in a garden, undated; cuid1317 (Photo-album 9, Image 48)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret, undated; cuid1318 (Photo-album 9, Image 49)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret, Alessandra Pandolfini and Ferruccio Marchi at the publishers Centro Di, Firenze, undated; cuid1319 (Photo-album 9, Image 50)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret at the Museo Bardini, Firenze, undated; cuid1320 (Photo-album 9, Image 51)
      - HA with a man outside the Baptistery of Parma, undated; cuid1321 (Photo-album 9, Image 52)
      - HA with a couple at a restaurant [Anne and Michael Rosse], undated; cuid1322 (Photo-album 9, Image 53)
      - HA at a dinner party, undated; cuid1323 (Photo-album 9, Image 54)
      - HA at a party, with two ladies (Titina Sartori on the left), undated; cuid1324 (Photo-album 9, Image 55)
      - HA with Alexander Zielcke and Merritt Cootes and others, 1967; cuid1325 (Photo-album 9, Image 56)
        Annotated on the verso by Merritt Cootes. Color print.
      - HA with a lady at a party, undated; cuid1326 (Photo-album 9, Image 57)
      - HA with a man, undated; cuid1327 (Photo-album 9, Image 58)
      - HA at a dinner party (Joan Haslip second on the right), undated; cuid1328 (Photo-album 9, Image 59)
      - HA with others including Mary Koch and Boris Baronovic at Spoleto, July 2, 1973; cuid1329 (Photo-album 9, Image 60-65.)
        Color prints, annotated on the verso.
      - HA with others including Carel Johnson, a governor of the British Institute at Villa Capponi, Arcetri, Firenze, undated; cuid1330 (Photo-album 9, Image 66-67.)
      - HA with a lady, 1975; cuid1331 (Photo-album 9, Image 68)
      - HA with a lady and man, undated; cuid1332 (Photo-album 9, Image 69)
      - HA with a couple in a restaurant, undated; cuid1333 (Photo-album 9, Image 70-71.)
      - HA at a dinner party (including Merritt Cootes), undated; cuid1334 (Photo-album 9, Image 72-73.)
      - HA with two ladies, 1985; cuid1335 (Photo-album 9, Image 74)
        Annotated on the verso "Casa Finaly, 1985", Color print.
      - HA with Michael Crawcour at San Miniato al Monte, Firenze, 1983; cuid1336 (Photo-album 9, Image 74a.-74b.)
        Annotated on the verso by Crawcour. Color prints.
      - HA with a lady, undated; cuid1337 (Photo-album 9, Image 75)
        Photo by Desmond O'Neill, Oxshott, Surrey, GB
      - HA [with Joan Haslip], undated; cuid1338 (Photo-album 9, Image 76)
        Oversize, I.C.12.9. folder 98.
      - HA with two ladies, undated; cuid1339 (Photo-album 9, Image 77-78.)
      - HA with a lady at the wedding of Angelica Frescobaldi, Villa I Collazzi, Firenze, 13 July, 1985; cuid1340 (Photo-album 9, Image 79)
        Name annotated on the verso but illegible. Color print.
      - HA with a lady, undated; cuid1341 (Photo-album 9, Image 80)
        Color prints. At Villa I Collazzi, Firenze.
      - HA at a party [Palazzo Corsini, Firenze ], with puppies. Those present include: Fiamma Ferragamo, Nanni Guisu, Mina Gregori, Giorgiana Corsini, Lottie Antinori, Lalli Marchi, Filippo Corsini, John Bradamas, Annalu Samminiatelli (née Corsini), Titina Sartori, Maria Antinori, Nannina Fossi, and 'Cika' Marzotto, undated; cuid1342 (Photo-album 9, Image 80a.-109b.)
      - HA with a lady, undated; cuid1343 (Photo-album 9, Image 109c.)
      - HA with a group of Chinese friends and others in a Chinese restaurant, undated; cuid1344 (Photo-album 9, Image 109d.)
      - HA with friends, undated; cuid1345 (Photo-album 9, Image 109e.)
      - HA with a man [at Positano (Salerno) or with Francis Steegmuller on Capri], 1981; cuid1346 (Photo-album 9, Image 110-111.)
      - HA with HRH the Prince of Wales and Lady Diana and Maria Fossi Todorow at the Galleria degli Uffizi, Firenze, 1985; cuid1347 (Photo-album 9, Image 112)
      - HA with a man beside a swimming pool, undated; cuid1348 (Photo-album 9, Image 113)
        Oversize, I.C.12.9. folder 99.
      - HA with a lady at Marlia (Lucca), 15 September, 1985; cuid1349 (Photo-album 9, Image 114)
      - HA with two men, undated; cuid1350 (Photo-album 9, Image 115)
      - HA with David Rundle and Giulia Fermi and others at a party at the British Institute of Florence held on the occasion of her retirement, [15 May], 1985; cuid1351 (Photo-album 9, Image 115a.)
      - HA with Giulia Fermi at a party at the British Institute of Florence held on the occasion of her retirement, [15 May], 1985; cuid1352 (Photo-album 9, Image 115b.)
      - HA with HRH the Queen Mother at Marlia (Lucca) and others, 1986; cuid1353 (Photo-album 9, Image 116-118.)
        Color prints, June 24 1986. Annotated on the verso.
      - HA with others at parties, undated; cuid1354 (Photo-album 9, Image 119-123.)
      - HA at a dinner party, 1988; cuid1355 (Photo-album 9, Image 124-125.)
      - HA with Mary Ellen Bradamas at a restaurant, ca. 1991; cuid1356 (Photo-album 9, Image 126)
        Oversize, I.C.12.9. folder 100.
    - 13 HA with guests at Villa La Pietra
      - HA in the gardens of Villa La Pietra as a page (with his brother WA) in a wedding photograph at the marriage of Louise Gaylord with Walter Dillingham. Wedding guests included Mrs Gerritt Wilder, Gov. and Mrs George Carter, Mr and Mrs. Von Holt,(under obelisk) John Miller, best man, next to Italia Blair de Soriano, Louise's cousin and matron of honour, AA and HMA(next to Italia), Margaret Hamill, bridesmaid(next to HMA), Monsieur and Madame Max Henraux, Polly and Harry MacFarlane, Olive Olga Ogelsby, Louise's godmother, Mrs Albert Spalding, mother of the famous violinist, Dr Charles Adams, Louise's step-father, and her mother Bess Adams(fourth from the right), and Mr and Mrs Potter Palmer, the famous art collectors of Chicago May, 1910; cuid1357 (Photo-album 9, Image 127)
        See also I.C.2.6.,122-123.
        Oversize, I.C.13.9. folder 101.
      - [HA as a boy] with friends outside Villa La Pietra, ca. 1915; cuid1358 (Photo-album 9, Image 128-133.)
        Negs.and print.
      - HA with a friend in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, ca. 1920; cuid1359 (Photo-album 9, Image 134)
      - HA with a couple in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1360 (Photo-album 9, Image 135-136.)
      - HA with a lady in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1361 (Photo-album 9, Image 137)
      - HA with a couple and AA in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Giardino Topiario), undated; cuid1362 (Photo-album 9, Image 138)
      - HA and HMA in the interior of Villa La Pietra, [with Chien], ca. 1950; cuid1363 (Photo-album 9, Image 139-140.)
      - HA with friends in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Peristilio della glicine), undated; cuid1364 (Photo-album 9, Image 141-143a.)
      - HA with a lady in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Scalone of the Vasche), undated; cuid1365 (Photo-album 9, Image 144)
      - HA with a man and two ladies in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1366 (Photo-album 9, Image 145)
      - HA with a couple in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1367 (Photo-album 9, Image 146-147.)
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, 1954; cuid1368 (Photo-album 9, Image 148)
      - Ha with a girl in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), 1958; cuid1369 (Photo-album 9, Image 149)
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1370 (Photo-album 9, Image 150-152.)
      - HA with a lady in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Prima Vasca), 1964; cuid1371 (Photo-album 9, Image 153)
      - HA with a man in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Terrazza, Vista del Colosso, and Teatrino), undated; cuid1372 (Photo-album 9, Image 154-159.)
      - HA with guests, and Alexander Zielcke, in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino, Boschetto - Vista dell'Arco), undated; cuid1373 (Photo-album 9, Image 160-164.)
      - HA with guests [including Jean and Merritt Cootes] in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (the Terrazza), undated; cuid1374 (Photo-album 9, Image 164a.)
      - HA dancing [with Margot Fonteyn] in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), ca.1960; cuid1375 (Photo-album 9, Image 165)
        Photo by Cecil Beaton signed on the recto.
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret and Lord Snowdon in the interior of Villa La Pietra, ca. 1965; cuid1376 (Photo-album 9, Image 166)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret and Lord Snowdon and others [Princess Irene of Greece and Queen Frederica of Denmark] in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Terrazza), ca. 1965; cuid1377 (Photo-album 9, Image 167-169.)
      - HA at a Christmas party with others including Alexander Zielcke [in Villa La Pietra], undated; cuid1378 (Photo-album 9, Image 169a.-169b.)
      - HA and Alexander Zielcke in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, ca. 1965; cuid1379 (Photo-album 9, Image 169c.-169e.)
      - HA at the entrance to Villa La Pietra with a couple [Mr and Mrs Fosburgh], 1965; cuid1380 (Photo-album 9, Image 170-171.)
        Annotated on the verso "photographed by Reginald Colby, August 1965".
      - HA with a man, 1965; cuid1381 (Photo-album 9, Image 171a.)
        Annotated on the verso "Aout 1965".
      - HA and Alexander Zielcke, undated; cuid1382 (Photo-album 9, Image 171b.)
        Two attached photos.
      - HA with Alexander Zielcke, undated; cuid1383 (Photo-album 9, Image 171c.)
        Three attached photos.
      - HA, undated; cuid1384 (Photo-album 9, Image 171d.)
      - HA at the entrance to Villa La Pietra with two ladies, undated; cuid1385 (Photo-album 9, Image 172-174.)
      - HA with two ladies in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, October, 1969; cuid1386 (Photo-album 9, Image 175)
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Terrazza), including Elena Marchi née Bartolomei, 1967; cuid1387 (Photo-album 9, Image 176)
        Dated on the verso. Color print.
      - HA with guests [including Mary Koch] in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Tempietto), ca. 1976; cuid1388 (Photo-album 9, Image 177-179.)
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1389 (Photo-album 9, Image 180)
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (the Tempietto), undated; cuid1390 (Photo-album 9, Image 180a.-180b.)
      - HA with a Chinese friend inside Villa La Pietra (the Biblioteca), undated; cuid1391 (Photo-album 9, Image 180c.)
      - HA with a lady guest in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (on the Scalone with the Seconda Vasca, and on the Terrazza), undated; cuid1392 (Photo-album 9, Image 180d.-180e.)
      - HA with Michael and Anne Rosse in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Terrazza), undated; cuid1393 (Photo-album 9, Image 181-184.)
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, July, 1971; cuid1394 (Photo-album 9, Image 185-188.)
        Dated on the verso. Color prints.
      - Ha with guests in the interior of Villa La Pietra (Salone), undated; cuid1395 (Photo-album 9, Image 189)
      - HA with friends from China in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino, Pomario), June, 1972; cuid1396 (Photo-album 9, Image 190-192.)
      - HA with a friend from China in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Giardino Segreto, Prima Vasca, Terrazza), February, 1972; cuid1397 (Photo-album 9, Image 193-196.)
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Giardino Segreto), Amis du Louvre, October, 1973; cuid1398 (Photo-album 9, Image 197)
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Prato del Cedro), undated; cuid1399 (Photo-album 9, Image 198)
      - HA with Masaaki Kara[shima] and Frederick Koch in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Prato ovale, Terrazza), July 9, 1974; cuid1400 (Photo-album 9, Image 199-200.)
        Annotated on the verso. Color prints.
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino, Pomario - interior of the Limonaia), April, 1973; cuid1401 (Photo-album 9, Image 201-203.)
      - HA with a guest in the interior of Villa La Pietra (Dining Room), 1974; cuid1402 (Photo-album 9, Image 203a.)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret in the interior of Villa La Pietra (Sala da Pranzo), 1974; cuid1403 (Photo-album 9, Image 204)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret in the interior of Villa La Pietra (Salone), 1974; cuid1404 (Photo-album 9, Image 205)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret in the interior of Villa La Pietra, 1974; cuid1405 (Photo-album 9, Image 206)
      - HA with HRH Princess Margaret, with the Queen of Rumania, in the interior of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1406 (Photo-album 9, Image 207)
      - HA with Mimì Nolan and two girls, Tina and Jenny in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Giardino Segreto), [22 November], 1974; cuid1407 (Photo-album 9, Image 207a.)
        Annotated on the verso, Color print.
      - Mimì Nolan with Dino and the staff of Villa La Pietra (at the front entrance), with two girls, Tina and Jennifer, [22 November], 1974; cuid1408 (Photo-album 9, Image 207b.)
      - HA with Mimì and Jim Nolan, with Tina [in the gardens of Villa La Pietra], [22 November], 1974; cuid1409 (Photo-album 9, Image 207c.)
      - HA with Jim Nolan and Kathy O'Leary and others in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (the Scalone), [22 November], 1974; cuid1410 (Photo-album 9, Image 207d.)
      - Mimì Nolan inside Villa La Pietra on the Scalone, [22 November], 1974; cuid1411 (Photo-album 9, Image 207e.)
      - HA with two girls, in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (the Terrazza), [22 November], 1974; cuid1412 (Photo-album 9, Image 207f.)
        Annotated on the verso by the Nolans, Color print.
      - HA with Mimì Nolan and a girl, in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (the Terrazza), [22 November], 1974; cuid1413 (Photo-album 9, Image 207g.)
      - HA with three girls in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (the Scalone), [22 November], 1974; cuid1414 (Photo-album 9, Image 207h.)
      - HA with Mimì Nolan and Marietta [in the gardens of Villa La Pietra], [22 November], 1974; cuid1415 (Photo-album 9, Image 207i.)
      - HA with a lady visitor in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Scalone, Terrazza, Prima Vasca, Teatrino), July, 1976; cuid1416 (Photo-album 9, Image 208-213.)
      - Ha with a couple in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1417 (Photo-album 9, Image 214)
      - HA with two men guests in the interior of Villa La Pietra (Salone), undated; cuid1418 (Photo-album 9, Image 215-216.)
      - HA with two men guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), undated; cuid1419 (Photo-album 9, Image 217)
        Color print. See 215-216.
      - HA with a couple in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1420 (Photo-album 9, Image 217a.)
      - Ha with a man in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Prima Vasca), undated; cuid1421 (Photo-album 9, Image 218-219.)
      - HA at the entrance to Villa La Pietra, with a man guest and Alexander Zielcke, undated; cuid1422 (Photo-album 9, Image 220)
      - HA with a member of the film crew of London Weekend Television, and the butler Dino at the entrance to Villa La Pietra, 1976; cuid1423 (Photo-album 9, Image 221)
      - HA with Russell Harty, London Weekend Television, in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), 1976; cuid1424 (Photo-album 9, Image 222-223.)
      - HA with a member of the film crew of London Weekend Television in the interior of Villa La Pietra (Sala da Pranzo), 1976; cuid1425 (Photo-album 9, Image 224-227.)
      - HA with Russell Harty, and a member of the film crew of London Weekend Television, in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Terrazza), 1976; cuid1426 (Photo-album 9, Image 228-231.)
      - HA at the entrance to Villa La Pietra with members of the film crew of London Weekend Television, 1976; cuid1427 (Photo-album 9, Image 232)
      - HA being filmed by London Weekend Television in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, 1976; cuid1428 (Photo-album 9, Image 233-234.)
      - HA with a man and girl in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Scalone), 1977; cuid1429 (Photo-album 9, Image 235)
        Color print, September 1977
      - HA with guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Pergola delle Rose, Prima Vasca), April, 1977; cuid1430 (Photo-album 9, Image 236-240.)
      - HA with a couple, ca. 1978; cuid1431 (Photo-album 9, Image 241-242.)
      - HA with Emma Bowden, Stefano Romei, Kate Bowden, Rebecca Hill, [Gerald] Bowden, in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), undated; cuid1432 (Photo-album 9, Image 243)
        Color print, annotated on the verso.
      - HA with a girl in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Peristilio della Glicine), undated; cuid1433 (Photo-album 9, Image 243a.)
      - HA with a group of guests in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Terrazza), undated; cuid1434 (Photo-album 9, Image 244)
      - HA with participants of the Congresso Amici dei Musei in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Terrazza), 1978; cuid1435 (Photo-album 9, Image 245)
      - HA with two men, January, 1978; cuid1436 (Photo-album 9, Image 246-247.)
      - HA with a lady in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Vialone), 1979; cuid1437 (Photo-album 9, Image 248)
      - HA with a man in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, 1979; cuid1438 (Photo-album 9, Image 249)
      - HA with a couple in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Scalone), undated; cuid1439 (Photo-album 9, Image 250)
      - HA with Gordon Barrass [and his first wife] in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), undated; cuid1440 (Photo-album 9, Image 250a.)
      - HA with Gordon Barrass and another man in the gardens of Villa La Pietra [Vista del Duomo], undated; cuid1441 (Photo-album 9, Image 250b.)
      - HA with Gordon Barrass in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), undated; cuid1442 (Photo-album 9, Image 250c.)
      - HA with a boy in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Prima Vasca and Pomario), ca. 1970s; cuid1443 (Photo-album 10, Image 1-5.)
      - HA with a boy and another man in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1444 (Photo-album 10, Image 6)
      - HA with Alexander Zielcke and another man in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1445 (Photo-album 10, Image 7)
      - HA with a boy in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Pomario), undated; cuid1446 (Photo-album 10, Image 8-9.)
        See #1-5.
        Oversize, I.C.13.10. folder 102.
      - HA with John Bradamas, President of NYU in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (the Terrazza), April, 1983; cuid1447 (Photo-album 10, Image 9a.-9b.)
      - HA with John Bradamas, President of NYU in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (the Teatrino), April, 1983; cuid1448 (Photo-album 10, Image 9c.-9d.)
      - HA with a man in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Giardino Segreto), ca. 1982; cuid1449 (Photo-album 10, Image 10-11.)
        Color prints, ca. 1982
      - HA with John Bradamas, President of NYU in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Giardino Segreto, Pomario, Teatrino, Prima Vasca), April, 1983; cuid1450 (Photo-album 10, Image 12-19.)
      - HA with John Bradamas in the interior of Villa La Pietra, 1983; cuid1451 (Photo-album 10, Image 20)
      - HA with Mary Ellen, wife of John Bradamas in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Prima Vasca, Pomario, Vista dell'Arco, Teatrino), 1983; cuid1452 (Photo-album 10, Image 21-29.)
      - HA with Mary Ellen, wife of John Bradamas in the interior of Villa La Pietra, 1983; cuid1453 (Photo-album 10, Image 30)
      - HA with a couple in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), undated; cuid1454 (Photo-album 10, Image 31)
      - HA with Alexander Zielcke in the interior of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1455 (Photo-album 10, Image 32)
        Oversize, I.C.13.10. folder 103.
      - HA with a lady in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Vista del Colosso, Terrazza), undated; cuid1456 (Photo-album 10, Image 33-35.)
      - HA with a lady in the gardens of Villa La Pietra, undated; cuid1457 (Photo-album 10, Image 36)
      - HA with a group of French visitors in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Scalone), 7 June, 1983; cuid1458 (Photo-album 10, Image 36a.)
        All identified on the verso. Color print.
      - HA with a group of French visitors in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Teatrino), 7 June, 1983; cuid1459 (Photo-album 10, Image 36b.)
      - HA with a group of French visitors in the gardens of Villa La Pietra (Scalone), 7 June 1983 (Princesse Farman Farmaian, Madame Amic, Madame Hachette, and Madame de Guerre), cuid1460 (Photo-album 10, Image 36c.)
        All identified on the verso, Color print.